{
    "Quizes": [
        {
            "title": "Geography Quiz",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of the following countries does NOT border the Mediterranean Sea?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Egypt",
                        "France",
                        "Jordan",
                        "Turkey"
                    ],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Where is Mount Everest?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Bangladesh",
                        "Cambodia",
                        "India",
                        "Nepal"
                    ],
                    "answer": 3
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of the following is the name of an independent country?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Albania",
                        "Alberta",
                        "America",
                        "Athabaska"
                    ],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of the following countries is NOT in South America?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Argentina",
                        "Botswana",
                        "Colombia",
                        "Venezuela"
                    ],
                    "answer": 1
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of the Great Lakes is wholly contained in the USA?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Lake Erie",
                        "Lake Huron",
                        "Lake Michigan",
                        "Lake Ontario",
                        "Lake Superior"
                    ],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which country's flag does NOT contain the colour red?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Pakistan",
                        "Philippines",
                        "Poland",
                        "Portugal"
                    ],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "What is the former name of Istanbul?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Campala",
                        "Carthage",
                        "Constantinople",
                        "Crete"
                    ],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "The Great Barrier Reef is closest to which country?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Australia",
                        "Indonesia",
                        "Japan",
                        "Peru"
                    ],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of the following rivers is the longest?",
                    "choices": [
                        "The Danube River",
                        "The Saint Lawrence River",
                        "The Volga River",
                        "The Yellow River"
                    ],
                    "answer": 3
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Where is the Shwedagon Pagoda?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Laos",
                        "Myanmar",
                        "Sri Lanka",
                        "Thailand",
                        "Vietnam"
                    ],
                    "answer": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Number Systems",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "questionText": "If the binary number 110101001100 is converted to octal, how many digits will the octal number contain?",
                    "choices": [
                        "3",
                        "4",
                        "5",
                        "6",
                        "not enough information"
                    ],
                    "answer": 1
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "In the hexadecimal system, how many numbers are there between 58 and 62 (not including 58 and 62)?",
                    "choices": [
                        "3",
                        "6",
                        "9",
                        "12",
                        "not enough information"
                    ],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "In the octal number system, 77 + 1 = ?",
                    "choices": [
                        "78",
                        "80",
                        "100",
                        "777",
                        "none of the above"
                    ],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "If the left-most digit of a hexadecimal number is 1, and all of the other digits are 0, then number must be:",
                    "choices": [
                        "a power of 16",
                        "a power of 8",
                        "a power of 2",
                        "all of the above",
                        "none of the above"
                    ],
                    "answer": 3
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "16 ^ 2222 = ",
                    "choices": [
                        "2 ^ 8888",
                        "8 ^ 4444",
                        "10 ^ 6666",
                        "not enough information"
                    ],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "What is the decimal equivalent of the largest eight-digit binary number?",
                    "choices": [
                        "255",
                        "256",
                        "512",
                        "1000000",
                        "not enough information"
                    ],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of the following is a valid number in a base-6 system?",
                    "choices": [
                        "45",
                        "55",
                        "65",
                        "a and b",
                        "b and c",
                        "all of the above"
                    ],
                    "answer": 3
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "A bus can hold 24 passengers, and a car can hold 3 passengers. If every bus used must be full, what is the minimum number of vehicles needed to transport 100 people?",
                    "choices": [
                        "4",
                        "5",
                        "6",
                        "7",
                        "not enough information"
                    ],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of the following statements is true?",
                    "choices": [
                        "Every power of 8 is a power of 2",
                        "Every power of 8 is a power of 16",
                        "Every power of 2 is a power of 8",
                        "Every power of 16 is a power of 8."
                    ],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Let n be an integer greater than 1. Which of the following numbers is greater than 0?",
                    "choices": [
                        "n * n % n / n",
                        "n * n / n % n",
                        "n / n % n * n",
                        "n / n * n % n",
                        "n % n * n / n",
                        "n % n / n * n"
                    ],
                    "answer": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "OnePiece Quiz",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "questionText": "What is Luffy's bounty after the WholeCake Island Arc?",
                    "choices": ["500 Million", "150 Million", "300 Million", "320 Million", "1.5 Billion"],
                    "answer": 4
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Where was Gol D. Roger Born?",
                    "choices": ["East Blue", "West Blue", "Thriller Bark", "Alabasta"],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Who is Luffy's first main opponent?",
                    "choices": ["Buggy The Clown", "Arlong", "Alvida", "Kuro"],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of the following is not a type of Haki?",
                    "choices": ["Conquerer's", "Observation", "Armament", "Divinity"],
                    "answer": 3
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Who's the only character to eat more than 1 Devil Fruit?",
                    "choices": ["Shanks", "BlackBeard", "Fugitora", "WhiteBeard", "Hawkeye"],
                    "answer": 1
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "What is the name Luffy uses to enter the Colosseum in Dressrosa?",
                    "choices": ["Luffy (regular name)", "Lucy", "Lucky", "Loffy"],
                    "answer": 1
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Who is known as \"The Strongest Creature\" in the One Piece Universe?",
                    "choices": ["Gol D. Roger", "WhiteBeard", "Kaido", "Akainu", "BlackBeard"],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "How many swords does Roronoa Zoro wield?",
                    "choices": ["1", "2", "3", "none"],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "What was the name of the mountain bandit that kidnapped Luffy when he was a kid?",
                    "choices": ["Higuma", "Liguma", "Hijuma"],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Who is the Captain of the Heart Pirates?",
                    "choices": ["Trafalgar D. Law", "Crocodile", "Eustass Kidd", "Silvers Rayleigh"],
                    "answer": 0
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "How many of the eleven Supernovas are pirate ship captains?",
                    "choices": ["10", "8", "9", "11"],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "questionText": "Which of these characters were never one of the 'seven warlords' of the sea?",
                    "choices": ["BlackBeard", "WhiteBeard", "Jinbe", "Crocodile", "Trafalgar D. Law", "Boa Hancock"],
                    "answer": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}